[car starting]
[car revving]
[jazz music playing]
[Jerry] This is an eyebrow-frizzing,
retina-melting,
absurdly gorgeous
1969 Lamborghini P400S Miura.
Just 43 inches tall,
it is painted in Arancio Borealis,
-Italian for "orange."
-[engine revs]
It has a mid-engine 360-horsepower V12
mounted sideways.
And it's got eyelashes on its headlights.
Jesus!
It's incredibly masculine
and incredibly feminine at the same time.
It is, in my opinion,
the most beautiful car ever designed.
[car accelerates]
[phone ringing]
[Chris] Hello.
[Jerry] Hey, Rock.
What are you doing?
[Chris] I'm not doing much.
Outside my house.
[Jerry] It's nice out.
[Chris] It's amazing. It's beautiful.
[Jerry] How about some coffee?
[Chris] Let's do it.
[Jerry] Hi, I'm Jerry Seinfeld.
And this is
Comedians in Cars Getting Coffee.
My guest today is my comedy buddy
and always brilliant, Chris Rock.
[Chris] SeinTime.
[Jerry] So this is it.
[Chris] This is my Tony Soprano house.
[Jerry] You're a made guy.
Where's Carm?
[Chris] Wow!
-What is this?
-It's the most beautiful car in the world.
[engine revving]
All right, here we go.
Is this thing gonna take off?
Yes, it is.
[Jerry] When this car
came on the scene in '66,
it was so shocking and so different,
it blew everybody else away.
So it reminds me of you.
[Chris] So it's a screaming person,
black car.
[both laughing]
[Jerry] It is. It screams.
[car speeds up]
How do you like the car?
-I like you, Jerry.
-Thank you, Chris.
And I say everything's about company.
A gourmet meal with an asshole...
-[Jerry laughing]
-...is a horrible meal.
A hotdog with an interesting person...
-Is a great meal. It's an amazing meal.
-...is an amazing meal.
[Chris] It's all about the company.
If we were in a cab,
we'd probably be having
the same, exact conversation.
[Chris] I remember your assistant
took your car that time.
[Jerry] To get his cousin out of jail.
-Whatever, he just took your car.
-And parked it...
Don't still buy his story ten years later.
Well...
'Cause there's no other way
to get your cousin out of jail.
[Jerry chuckles]
Nope, you got to do five more years
'cause someone had the nerve
to pick you up in a cheap car.
Here's my good jail story.
My brother was in the halfway house,
in between jail and whatever.
So, one day I'm dropping him off at jail,
and then I realize,
I'm waiting for him
to safely get into jail.
[laughing]
God forbid something happened to him
out here.
You know what, you're a good brother.
I'm a good brother.
People ask me for $5000 like it's asking,
"When's the next bus coming?"
[laughing]
"Hey, man, you got $5000?"
No one sits me down.
No one even tells me a story anymore.
They just ask me for $5000
like it's the time.
[laughing]
Like it's the time.
You can always tell people
who call you up for money.
"Hey, we need to talk."
"Aren't you talking now?"
[both chuckle]
"You need to corner me,
is that what you're suggesting?"
[laughing]
"Uh, I need to corner you later."
[both laughing]
Sometimes I try and figure out,
like, you take different inventions
and you put them
in a different time in history.
Like, if you were a caveman
and you had a lighter,
you'd be king of the world, right?
You'd be absolute king of the world.
If you were in the Civil War
and you had an AK-47,
-the war's over with one guy.
-One guy.
[Chris] When we were young comics,
we were looking for advantages.
Cheats, steroids.
Would I take a pill to be able to write
and direct a movie like Woody Allen?
You're goddamn right I would.
-[growls]
-That's a horrible analogy.
[Chris] Steroids, I don't know.
It's just an advantage to make more money,
like any other business.
Every stockbroker had a cell phone,
and then one day
one guy had the BlackBerry.
And for about three months,
he had a humongous advantage
over everybody.
BlackBerries don't turn you
into Lyle Alzado.
Getting information quicker,
getting to the quarterback quicker.
Tell me the difference.
So, really, steroids don't bother you?
-Ridiculous.
-They bother me
because they influence kids.
They are kids.
These players are kids.
Hey, there's rules.
These guys broke the rules.
They should be punished.
There's math,
and then everything else is debatable.
[chuckles softly]
And now we are entering Jersey
where they pump gas for you.
-There's no self service in Jersey.
-Oh, really? Why?
Chris Christie, I guess.
I can't believe how close to the name
Chris Christie is to Krispy Kreme.
Have you eaten yet today?
[Chris] I've eaten some fruit today.
I'm doing a movie in a couple of months.
-But I'll actually eat a burger.
-[Jerry] You had KFC three nights ago.
So you cheat.
You gonna throw me out the Hall of Fame?
'Cause I had Kentucky Fried Chicken?
Two-piece with a biscuit
is one of the greatest meals
ever invented.
Have you ever had Popeyes?
Popeyes is too good.
After you have Popeyes,
you need one of those Men in Black
memory sticks to erase your memory,
or else you will come back to this place
-every day.
-Every day.
[train horn blows]
[Chris] I think Lola had a basketball game
out here this year.
My oldest daughter,
Lola, plays basketball.
[inaudible dialogue]
[indistinct chatter]
-How you doing?
-Good. Can I get you something to drink?
I would like to start with some coffee.
-I'll take coffee with cream.
-You got it.
[Chris] 10:00 p.m. Tonight Show,
that's Conan's fault.
Know what the problem is?
Conan's not a comedian.
-He's a talk-show host.
-Right.
And any comedian
would have spotted that a mile away.
-Right.
-'Cause we're used to getting booked.
We know what the day before,
the day after, we know what that means.
It's true, you would smell that, you go,
"What?
There's gonna be an hour of talk show?"
-"In front of mine. On a one-way street."
-[chuckles]
It's like, "I'm dating Beyoncé
and Alicia Keys." No, you're not.
You're gonna date one of them
or you're gonna lose both of them.
As my brother would say, "Pick a bitch."
The analogy always
has to be black artists, right?
Yeah, I'm black. Jerry, I'm trying to...
Hey, sugar's not a bad thing.
-Want sugar?
-Okay, the real sugar.
I'm looking at this thing like...
I'm gonna get the chicken salad.
It's probably the worst thing
you could eat on camera is chicken salad.
-Get some fries?
-Yeah, a basket of fries?
You all right. I like you.
Who do you envy?
I admire people that have breakdowns.
-You admire them?
-Yeah.
'Cause once you have a breakdown, then you
can clear the slate, and you're like...
Everything you do is, like...
Like Eliot Spitzer?
-If he really did something now...
-Yeah.
-Wow. Look at that.
Tiger Woods is back.
He's got a new girl.
And he's a guy that needs a relationship.
He's a guy that needs
to make that call every night.
"All right. I'm in."
-"Had a good round."
-"It was good."
I remember, years ago,
I guess Prince was married.
I was hanging out with Prince.
And he was like,
"Man, I gotta go make that call."
Prince, calling his wife,
"Yeah, okay. Yeah."
He made the most routine call
to his wife you could ever see.
That's all the marriage counseling
you really need.
Prince knew, "I gotta make this call."
[Jerry] My favorite thing is still
the thing you did to me.
-What was Oprah's play? The...
-The Color Purple?
The Color Purple.
And we were at the after-party
at the Four Seasons.
I was standing around, and I was
with Jess, we were schmoozing.
We locked eyes. You came over to me.
Remember this?
You grabbed my arms
and you went, "Comedian."
-I needed a comedian.
-I flash on that moment all the time.
Somebody was saying the other day about...
"Gotta be funny or they'll turn on you,"
a regular person told me.
"They will turn on you."
I go, "They should turn on you."
It's a very humbling life at any level.
-You can't cheat them.
-No.
The ability to talk
to a lot of people is freakish.
It's more freakish than being
able to run fast or dunk a basketball
or any of those other things.
It's freakish.
You think Superman could talk
to 1000 people at one time?
-[chuckling]
-Superman could, yeah.
He can get their attention,
'cause he has to bend something first.
But to just get up in front of 1000 people
and start talking?
They would give him a few minutes,
and then if he's not funny...
Yeah and every time he would lose,
he'd have to break something.
He'd lose the room. Eventually...
Or burn something
with his X-ray vision or something.
He'd fly, come back.
"Okay. I got your attention."
Any place I go, if there's a microphone,
people want me to speak.
A graduation, a book club thing,
a book signing...
Wherever there's a microphone,
someone's gonna come up to me and go...
-Yeah, we can...
-I can go to a stranger's funeral...
Have you ever talked at a funeral?
I talked at a friend's funeral this year.
Yeah.
Got a couple laughs.
[laughs]
The great thing about you,
there's no subject you cannot handle.
You have given some thought
to almost everything.
-We're professional arguers.
-Yeah.
Not only can we argue about anything,
we can argue either side.
I'm working on a bit about bullying.
Everybody's trying to get rid of bullying.
I'm like, "You crazy?"
Some of these kids need this.
I'll go even further.
Most of them need it.
Who's gonna cure AIDS?
Who's gonna invent the fuel
-that gets us off of fossil fuel?
-That's right.
-Who's gonna do these things?
-Yeah.
Some guy that was bullied,
that's who's gonna do it.
I know. My wife is always trying to stop
the boys from beating on each other.
I'm saying,
"No, they gotta learn, this is it."
-This is life.
-Does your wife do that?
Trying to stop the fights all the time?
-Wanting everything to be fair.
-You hate that.
I hate it. Lola had a basketball game.
Coach didn't put her in.
It was a real close game.
She's not the greatest. Didn't put her in.
Wife's pissed off.
I'm a little pissed, but my thing is,
"Hey, honey, you know,
there's a way to get in the game.
I'm just saying.
-[laughing]
-There's a way to get in the game."
Other than having your mother...
Yeah, I mean...
Some kids actually got in the game.
And I did tell my daughter after the game,
"You know, I used to go the comedy club.
And they would not put me on.
I'd get there at 7:45.
And I would wait until 1:30,
2:00 in the morning, and not get on.
But I worked on it.
I worked."
I'll tell you one of the great
activities is skateboarding.
-Mmm.
-To learn to do a skateboard trick,
how many times you gotta get something
wrong till you get it right?
And you keep falling
and you hurt yourself.
And you hurt yourself. And you learn to do
that trick, now you got a life lesson.
Whenever I see skateboard kids,
I think, "Those kids will be all right."
Yeah.
[jazz music playing]
So, did you actually say that line
to your wife?
-"There is a way to be..."
-No, I did not say that.
Why would you...
I'd advise against that, as your counsel.
-Here you go, guys. Thank you.
-Thanks very much.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
-[Jerry] Look at this car. Do you get...
-Now I'm impressed by it.
Amongst the pedestrian cars,
you're like...
Holy [beep].
-Thank you.
-Look at that.
[engine revving]
[Jerry] It's freakish
-for one person to talk to 1000.
-If you walked in one day
and you went to your kids' school,
and there were 500 kids
listening to your kid,
you'd think, like,
your kid was the devil or something.
My kid's possessed.
I had a Make-A-Wish kid,
like 15-year-old kid, dying of cancer.
And I snuck him the Pam Anderson sex tape.
In between all the other crap.
Here.
[chuckles]
He's dead now, but...
He lived a little more.
-He lived a little more.
-Yeah.
This is a very fast car, by the way.
Wow.
[increasing acceleration]
SeinTime's going fast.
There goes a cop.
And he's coming.
[laughing]
He's gonna...
Yup, he's coming.
What do you think? Do we get a ticket?
[laughing]
You want to bet $5000?
[both laughing]
[Chris] It'd be such a better episode
if he pulls me to the side and beats
the [beep] out of me, don't you think?
-[Chris] Did he give up?
-[Jerry] No, we got him.
[siren wailing]
Oh, boy.
Now, here's the crazy thing.
If you weren't here, I'd be scared.
[both laughing]
-Yeah, I'm famous. Still black.
-Well, let's not be...
Let's not be... Stop it. That's really...
I'd be babbling.
-Okay.
-That's terrible.
Right now, I'm looking
for my license right now.
[pulls handbrake]
Cut it off.
License and registration.
[officer talks over police radio]
[Chris] All right, he's got a crew cut.
-He means business.
-[laughing]
-You all right?
-Yeah, how's it going?
License and registration?
-Where you guys headed?
-We're going...
-Alpine.
-Alpine, New Jersey.
To Alpine, you're going the wrong way.
[indistinct talk over police radio]
-Is this your car?
-No, sir.
[sighing in exhaustion]
-Were you worried, Chris?
-I was worried the whole time.
I'm still worried.
[both chuckling]
Come on, it was fine.
[engine revs]
[car screeching]